FERNAN GONZALEZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I have been a Full Stack developer for six years. Throughout my career, I have specialized in the programming languages PHP and JavaScript. I had the opportunity to work for the Ministry of Economy and Finance, the Faculty of Architecture, and the Technological Laboratory of Uruguay. I am an easily adaptable person with a great ability to assimilate new concepts and generate creative solutions. I believe that teamwork is essential to create a positive work environment and to efficiently achieve established goals. Currently, I am a Computer Engineering student and I am seeking new challenges that will help me grow professionally.



+598 99 33 58 20



fernan7994@gmail.com



Linkedin profile



GitHub profile

EDUCATION

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

University of the Republic (UdelaR)

Unfinished

GENEXUS ANALYST

Jovenes a Programar (Plan Ceibal)

2017

PHP AND MYSQL PROGRAMMER

BIOS Systems School

2016

OTHERS

DEVOPS CULTURE AND MINDSET

University of California Web

2021

MACHINE LEARNING CON PYTHON

IBM Web

2018

FIRST CERTIFICATE IN ENGLISH

Cambridge University

2010

EXPERIENCE

TECHNOLOGICAL LABORATORY OF URUGUAY (LATU)

Full-Stack Developer (Contractor) 2018 - 2024

I developed various modules for LATU's ERP, with the most relevant ones being:

- Module for conducting inspections and certifications for temporary import admissions: Data loading development, Implementation of a responsive design for use by inspectors on-site, Compliant with printing certificates, Integration with a VUCE API.
- Module for the administration of inspections and certifications for the centralized procurement unit: Enabled client data loading. Facilitated the issuance of digitally signed certificates.
- Modifications to different modules such as work requests, tickets, and hour budgeting: Made adjustments and improvements to various system modules.
- Key skills used: PHP, JavaScript, AJAX, SQL (Microsoft and Oracle), API handling, SOAP, TCPDF, Requirements gathering.

Junior Developer 2017- 2018

I developed and updated various modules for LATU's ERP, with the most relevant ones being:

- CMS Module for Training Courses: Creation and publication of training courses on the portal, Issuance of completion certificates.
- Module for Invoice Management: Data loading, authorizations, and compliance checks, Connection through APIs to SICFE (Electronic Invoicing) and SAP (Accounting Module).
- Key skills used: PHP, JavaScript, AJAX. SQL (Microsoft and Oracle), API handling, SOAP, JSON, TCPDF, Requirements gathering.

FERNAN GONZALEZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Data Bases:

- MySQL
- Oracle SQL
- Microsoft SQL Server
- MongoDB (Academic)
- AWS (Academic)

Programming Lenguages:

- PHP, Laravel
- JavaScript, JQuery, ReactJS
- HTML5
- CSS3, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap
- Phyton (Academic)
- C++ (Academic)
- Genexus (Academic)

Other Skills:

- APIs Development and Consumption
- SOAP
- Git y GitHub (Trunk Based)
- Agile methodologies, Scrum
- CI/CD
- Docker (Academic)
- Kubernetes (Academic)
- Jenkins (Academic)

NATIONAL DIRECTION OF LOTTERIES AND POOLS (DNLQ)

Full-Stack Developer (Contractor) 2020 - 2021

Update of the PHP components of the DNLQ from imperative to OOP programming, as well as a redesign of the front-end interface in accordance with the visual styles of government websites. Key technologies: PHP, Bootstrap, Oracle SQL, research, and presentation of different options.

FACULTY OF ARCHITECTURE, DESIGN AND URBANISM (FADU)

Full-Stack Developer (Contractor) 2019 - 2020

Development of a CMS/ERP for the Continuing Education and Postgraduate Studies department at FADU. The system manages all aspects of administration, including:

- User and session creation
- User authorization
- Form creation for registrations
- User registrations for these forms
- Various compliance requirement controls
- Payment handling
- Visualization and export of related statistical data.

Key skills: Laravel, Boostrap, Javascript, MySQL, GIT, Requirements Gathering.